officef5.com 2013-03-24

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us, and we will treat your data with care and respect. We know that you care how information and data about you is collected, used and shared. This Privacy Statement describes our privacy policy and details how we collect, use, and/or disseminate the information you provide. We reserve the right change this Statement at any time and urge you to review our Statement regularly to familiarize yourself with any changes. 

**By visiting our website, using our online products/services, and/or by voluntarily submitting information to us via online forms, advertisement responses, and/or electronic mail, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Statement.**

**Who We Are**  
OfficeVP, LLC. has developed and licenses a system software product called OfficeF5 which allows Independent Marketing Agents to promote a legal and ethical network marketing opportunity and/or Client program and/or opportunities or programs and/or products of their choice. The OfficeF5 is designed to be used exclusively to promote the products and Services offered by the system. However, due to the fact that each OfficeF5 account is controlled by an independent representative, we cannot guarantee how the system and privacy information will be managed by these representatives.

OfficeVP, LLC. operates and manages the OfficeF5 strictly as a back-bone technology provider. Individuals that subscribe to the OfficeF5 do so in one of two forms: prospects (sometimes referred to as Pre-Enrollees), and Members. Individual subscriptions to the OfficeF5 are referred to as a "Member" in the OfficeF5.

To cater to both you (the Customer) and our Members, we may be required to collect, use, and share certain information. The type of information we collect, together with a description of how we use and/or share it, is described below. 

**Information Collection and Use  
**Your personal information (and your customer information) will be kept strictly confidential. It is never sold, given away, or shared with anyone, unless we're required to by law. 

Your recipient lists are stored on the OfficeF5 server. We do not, under any circumstances, steal your list, sell your list, or share it with any other party, unless required to by law. Your recipient list is kept strictly confidential. 

Only carefully selected, authorized personnel have access (for customer service and abuse-monitoring purposes) to view system accounts and campaigns. 

**Use of Web Technologies**   
We use a variety of technologies on our sites. Among these are cookies; a piece of information that our websites provide to your browser when you visit our sites. Cookies allow us to verify the login status of customers using products or services linked directly with our website, track point of entry to point of registration for those users participating in our affiliate signup programs, and to track and measure the success of a particular marketing campaign. Cookies also allow us to track overall site usage and determine areas users prefer, enabling us to make your visit to our websites easier by recognizing you when you return and helping to provide you with a customized experience. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. If you choose to disable cookies, you may still use our site; however, you may have limited access to some areas within our websites.

We may access and set cookies using web beacons, also known as single-pixel GIFs which are invisible graphical images. These web beacons provide us useful information regarding our site such as which pages users access. When we send you emails, we may include a single-pixel GIF to allow us to determine the number of people who open our emails. When you click on a link in an email, we record this individual response to allow us to customize our offerings to you.

We also keep track of activity on our website via log files stored on our web servers. We collect information such as IP address, browser type and version, and pages you view. We also keep track of how you got to our site and any links you click on to leave our site. Once you leave our site, we do not track you. We use your website activity to assist us in offering you a personalized Web experience, assist you with technical support, diagnose problems with our server, administer our websites and to tailor our product and service offerings to you. 

**Security**   
We take every precaution to protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information by using industry-recognized security safeguards such as firewalls, coupled with carefully developed security procedures to protect your information from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration. When we ask for sensitive information, such as credit card numbers, we protect it through the use of encryption during transmission, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Choice/Opt-out**   
OfficeF5 provides users the opportunity to opt-in, opt-out via a link in the footer of most email messages. These options are made available when you sign-up for our email lists and in email messages delivered from our company. Alternatively, you may email us at [support@officef5.com](mailto:support@officef5.com). 

Some communications (e.g. important account notifications and billing information) are necessary for all OfficeF5 customers. You must cancel your OfficeF5 account to unsubscribe from these communications. To cancel your OfficeF5 account, please email us at [support@officef5.com](mailto:support@officef5.com)[](mailto:support@constantcontact.com).
